All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece
must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber
after eating the gum gum fruit,
sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm going to be the king of the pirates!
Two years have passed since the War of the Best in Marine Form.
Reuniting after their special training,
Luffy and his crew continue on to the New World.
Their first stop is Fishman Island,
thousands of feet below sea level,
where they meet King Neptune.
Is to invite you all to the Ryugu Palace!
The Ryugu Palace, taken by the shark that they saved.
A few hours before Luffy met with King Neptune,
something unexpected happened.
An unfortunate encounter with a barrel at Mermaid Cove.
Geez, they sure sealed this thing tight!
There must be something important in there!
Well, let's think.
It's packed up all nice like a treasure chest,
but it's still a barrel, so...
maybe some fancy booze?
Oh, come on! Almost there!
That'll be enough! Just give me a second!
Ah!
That's right! Stand back!
Thank you very much, ladies!
But I think I can take it from here!
You mean there was a person stuffed in there?
No way!
I'm free!
Thank you so much for your help!
I truly couldn't have done it without you!
There's no need to run away!
Hurry! Get to the water!
Ah!
Too bad! Too slow!
Whoa!
What is this?
I'm sinking!
It's mud!
But where did it all come from?
How very observant of you,
though it's more like quicksand, technically.
Consider it my own personal swarm!
This is the power of the Swamp Swamp Fruit!
Hardly glamorous, but I don't mind!
Oh, and by the way, I wouldn't struggle if I were you!
Ah!
No!
It only makes you sink faster!
Someone help!
Oh, stop screaming!
I'm not gonna kill you!
I'll just suck you into a mucky hellhole!
Help me!
What?
Are you brain-dead, lady?
I said stop screaming, didn't I?
Just give it up already!
Initially!
You're fine!
Calm down and take a nap, why don't you?
Hee hee!
Hee hee hee!
Hee hee hee hee!
It's a good thing my body's a bottomless pit,
since there's plenty more treasure to put in it!
Huh.
Let me think here, how much do mermaids sell for?
Seventy million at auction, right?
And I nabbed three of them!
That is quite the catch, I must say!
Hee hee hee hee hee!
Those stupid straw hats help me out after all!
If it gets me a free pass through immigration,
you can lock me in a barrel any time!
So what if my plan to cash in on their bounties
didn't quite pan out?
Now I can steal all the mermaids I want!
Hee hee hee hee hee hee hee!
Hmm.
Isshili!
Where'd she run off to?
I'm sure I heard her call for help.
Oh, Isshili!
Back in the present.
In the Port Town of Coral Hill.
Located in the Ryuugu Kingdom.
The Straw Hat Pirates!
They must be the ones who kidnapped your friends from Mermaid Cove!
Who else could it have been?
Hold on.
They saved Kaimi from kidnappers!
I'm sure you must be mistaken.
They were nice. They aren't here to cause any trouble.
Maybe they needed a hostage.
But why?
First off, let's look at the facts.
Excluding us guards and you mermaids, there was nobody else at the cove around that time.
And those thugs from the Fishman District were forced to flee.
A number of the Straw Hats left, but a portion of the crew is still unaccounted for.
We don't know what their intentions may be.
The temptation for humans to kidnap mermaids is just too great.
They're traded at a high price all over the world and we have criminals like them to thank.
But they weren't just any pirates. They saved Kami from slavery.
Pirates often make friends with mermaids.
And then when they come down here, they use that relationship to kidnap them.
Prince Fukuboshi!
Are you certain, Madam Charlie, this vision that you saw?
It is of dire importance, so I must be sure of its accuracy.
Your silence speaks volumes.
Then it is as you say, Straw Hat will bring ruin to this island.
Here, Madam Charlie. I brought you some water.
It's true. I saw it all loud and clear. Such an awful future.
The accuracy of your predictions is well known.
I'm convinced that we must approach this matter with the utmost caution.
It is quite the shame, though.
They seem to have a good reputation with the mermaids, and they saved my sister's pets, so I wanted to treat them kindly.
But now that this new development has come to light, I fear that I must keep a close eye on them.
We have no choice but to take them all into custody.
Around the same time, nearby in the high-class district known as Fishfilly Hills.
They're gone.
Those weren't just ordinary pirates, were they?
Otherwise, King Neptune wouldn't have given them a personal invitation to Ryugu Palace, huh?
Careful you don't fall.
Neptune!
Whoooo!
Ja, ja!
Ja, mon. Ja, mon. Ja, mon. Ja, mon. Ja, mon. Ja, mon. Ja, mon. Ja, mon.
Neptune!
Qu simplicity!
I don't get it...
What's Jamon?!
Sounds dumb to me!
Ahahaha!
God, are you stupid or just playing crazy?!
You got invited to the royal palace!
DON'T BE A PUNK!
Ha ha ha!
You have no idea how much my daughter loves that shark.
It's her favorite pet.
Mmm.
Megalo's never coming back, she said.
Tears welling up in her eyes.
I had no idea that he'd been attacked by the Kraken.
You have my gratitude for rescuing him from danger.
Cha-cha!
I can't really take credit, but whatever.
It all worked out.
So the princess has a shark for a pet, huh?
Oh, what's that, Papagu?
Could it be that you're not as intimate with the princess as you claim?
It did sound fishy.
Aquatic puns aside, I feel so bad for Sanji.
He's stuck in bed,
and he wanted to see the mermaid princess more than anyone else.
He's had a lot of bad luck lately, and it hasn't even been his fault.
Mostly.
But if she's got a pet shark, she might be kind of intense.
Are you sure this is okay?
I mean, someone like me going to Ryugu Palace.
He said we could bring our friends, and you guys definitely make the cut.
This is a rare opportunity.
Just enjoy it.
And if you think it's bad, enjoy it even more.
Ha-ha-ha.
By the way, I sent my sons to fetch you, but they took too long and I grew impatient.
I hope they returned in the meantime.
We're holding a banquet, you see, and I simply can't stand to wait on any more guests.
I think we're going to get along great.
Crew, stop drooling!
Oh, speaking of guests, I already invited one of your crewmates.
He's at the palace now.
Huh?
I must say he was a bit lacking in manners, though.
He started drinking before the banquet and wouldn't listen to reason when I advised him to wait for the other guests to arrive.
I seem to have forgotten his name.
Gotta be Zoro.
That's Zoro.
Zori!
It's Zoro, okay?
Zoro!
Don't worry.
As surely as they found him, my soldiers will find the rest of your crew and bring them to the palace.
Hey, got any idea where everyone else went, Nami?
Oh, uh...
Oh, so many cool shops down here!
Not to mention plenty of people.
If we ask around enough, I'm sure somebody will have the info we're looking for.
Oh, yeah? Then do you want to handle it?
If you're looking to shop, that's fine.
But I've got an errand of my own I'd like to take care of.
This is where my old shipwright master came from.
If his family is still down here, I want him to know what an inspiration he was, and that he was a true man to the bitter end.
I know we just got back together, but if you don't mind, I'd like to do this on my own.
It sounds like it's pretty important, so sure.
There's something I'd like to see while we're here, too.
Oh, okay.
It's not often that I get to explore a culture that's completely removed from the surface world.
Someone with a discerning eye may uncover its secrets, or even some pieces of a forgotten history.
That's a Robin thing.
For sure.
So we split up again, but it wasn't a big deal.
No trouble on your end, right?
Uh, well, maybe an itty-bitty bit.
Hey, Fish King, I have a question.
That's not Neptune the god of the sea to you!
If we're 10,000 meters below sea level, why is it so bright and sunny everywhere we go?
Well, that's likely what our ancestors thought when they first arrived here.
This is the only place in the deep sea that light reaches.
It is a glorious, glowing beacon for all of fish mankind, and has been for as long as anyone can remember.
We owe it all to the giant Suntree Eve, whose mighty roots stretch to these depths, carrying shimmering sunlight along with them.
Suntree?
So are its roots bioluminescent, or does it just transfer sunlight from the surface?
The latter, it seems, though scientists have puzzled over the specifics for ages.
The respiration of its roots also supplies oxygen from the surface to our island.
Regardless, we owe our entire civilization to this single mystic tree.
So it's like the big brother, or in this case, big sister, of the mangroves in Sabaody.
Hey, hairy fish dude, I'm getting hungry!
Come on!
We'll be there soon.
It's huge!
That's the entrance.
Get ready.
Ha ha ha!
Ding dong.
Yeah?
Neptune.
Oh!
Hello, your highness!
Allow me to open the gate!
Here.
You'll want one of these.
Oh!
Yeah, what is it?
It's a bubbly coral.
It lets you make a little bubble whenever you want to.
Land dwellers don't visit often.
So much of the palace is submerged in water.
We don't want anyone drowning.
Can we take these as souvenirs?
Now forward.
Neptune!
It's fast!
This is fun, but I can't wait to see the palace.
I'm getting kind of nervous.
Yeah, I know.
It could be life-changing for me, too.
Just think.
What if this makes me even more famous?
Interesting.
So starfish can sweat.
Jamon, we're here.
We're here.
Whoa, those dragons are sweet.
Papaka's house seems positively shabby in comparison.
Hey, watch your mouth.
Buy me one of these, Luffy.
King Neptune has returned.
We were wondering where you ran off to.
Hurry, let them in.
Opening the gate.
Greetings, your highness.
Welcome back.
Now this is going to be fun.
Make yourselves at home.
You are my honored guests.
Not again.
And you brought guests along.
I've told you not to leave the palace on your own, but you don't listen to a word I say.
If you can't take guards and you can't inform your staff, then you can't leave the palace and that's final.
Shame on you, sir.
Ja, Moon.
It won't happen again.
He got scolded?
There are so many countless ways this could have gone wrong.
Our kingdom is in a volatile political state right now.
Surely as a king you realize that.
Can we just have the banquet already?
If you could stop scolding me, you'll notice that I brought back some very important people.
They're the pirates who saved Megalo from the kraken.
Huh?
Let's welcome them properly so I can maintain my dignity.
Hmm?
Where is Shirohoshi?
The princess should be here for this.
Actually, your highness, we had another incident.
And she found out?
Don't give her another thing to worry about.
She's a very delicate girl.
You know that.
Don't you give me that.
If you don't want your daughter to worry, then how about you stay here in the palace where it's safe instead of running off unguarded?
We thought you might be dead.
It won't happen again.
I promise.
Wow.
Again?
It's a bit unfortunate that you brought the guest yourself.
There was a development while you were out and a rather troubling one at that.
Indeed.
Prince Fukuboshi called and informed us of something better related and private.
Oh my goodness, this is quite awkward.
I trust our guests.
Out with it already.
That's the thing, sir.
So, are we eating or?
Hold on.
Where'd Luffy go?
He was here just a second ago.
He couldn't stand still for five minutes if his life depended on it.
This is the royal palace.
You don't just wander around here on your own.
I'm not here to watch some hairy fish dude get chewed out.
But I'm here to eat.
And I smell food this way.
Getting closer.
No water in here.
That's weird.
I can't smell anything now.
The food must be through those giant doors.
This place looks pretty fancy.
It must be the banquet hall.
Let's hope Zoro hasn't eaten all the good stuff.
But man, kind of intimidating, isn't it?
The doors are overkill.
I feel like I'm backing Impel down.
I really don't want people getting their food, huh?
That must mean whatever they've got in there is super good!
It's dark.
Why is it dark?
Well, who cares?
The food smells great.
Maybe it's going to be a surprise party.
Either way, I think I've waited long enough.
A little snack won't hurt.
Wait, is this the table?
Why is it squishy?
What is this?
Feels like some kind of coral, but why is it in a banquet hall?
Squishy again.
Weird.
If someone's here, could you turn on the lights?
Still really confused, but this sure is fun!
Hello, who's there?
What a horrid thing to do.
Bouncing on a poor, helpless girl such as myself.
Who are you, sir?
And what are you doing here?
Please don't hurt me.
That's one big lady.
I mean, big fish lady.
Have you come to kill me too?
Because I will have you now.
I'm not afraid.
No, not of you.
Not of anyone else either.
I am the daughter of King Neptune.
I'm not...
I'm not afraid of anything.
Nothing at all.
Someone help me!
Brother, please!
Hey, wait!
We didn't come here to kill you, okay?
Okay?
You suck, lady!
Shut up already!
The Mermaid Princess Shirohoshi has been confined to the Hard Shell Tower for years.
With its doors open for even a moment, Deccan launches an axe straight at her heart.
Meanwhile, things take a sour turn for the Straw Hat Pirates in the palace as Neptune's army suddenly surrounds them.
On the next, One Piece, a coward and a crybaby, the princess and the Hard Shell Tower.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!